Hello, Shiya.
How are you doing?
Stop it, Jingyan.
He's really busy.
Pei Song,
you're not coming to the last trip before the divorce?
Are you even human?
Shiya just wants to have something to remember it by.
Is it that hard for you?
Trip? What trip?
Bro,
are you pretending to have amnesia?
Pei Song.
Are you going on the trip tomorrow?
I want to have a memory before the divorce,
to make up for not having a honeymoon.
I don't think so.
R&D is quite busy lately,
so I don't have time.
Okay.
Pei Song.
I'll go.
Send me the address.
I mean I'll be right there.
Fine.
You know what's good for you.
I'll WeChat you. Hurry up.
Shiya, baby.
I'm exhausted.
I'm not doing it anymore.
I'm going to take a rest.
Pei Song.
Sorry.
I'm late.
Pei Ning,
do me a favor.
They happen to be free,
so I asked them to come.
You don't mind, do you?
Of course,
I mean of course not.
That's great.
Then it's settled.
Let you two gentlemen
set up the tent together.
Shiya, stop working.
Let's go.
Brother,
drink some water.
Thanks.
Let's set up the tent first.
Make it strong.
Who do you think will be faster?
I think...
It's done.
Shiya.
Jingyan,
bring your things here.
Coming.
Sorry,
Pei Song.
Shiya is mine tonight.
Brother.
See, I told you there's a bar here.
It's pretty nice.
Let's relax
and have a drink.
Shiya.
I'll go up for some fresh air.
I'll go with you.
I want to walk alone.
Um,
brother,
I'm going to the restroom.
Pei Song.
You've been married for three years.
Don't tell me you don't know
that Shiya's least favorite thing
is anything strawberry-flavored?
I really didn't know.
I thought all girls...
Straight man.
Jingyan.
I want to ask you,
is there any way to keep
Shiya and me from getting a divorce?
It's so cold.
I wonder if Shiya running out alone just now
without a coat,
is also feeling cold.
Thank you.
Blockhead.
Shiya.
I actually
really wish
I had met you
first.
Do you remember
when we were in college
and met for the first time?
It was so wonderful.
Unfortunately,
you disappeared later.
I couldn't find you no matter how hard I tried.
When we met again later,
you had become my brother's wife.
But you were just like in my memory,
so smart
and kind.
Actually, in front of my brother,
I, the younger brother,
was often ignored.
Only you
would talk to me first.
You are so good,
but he didn't know how to cherish you.
Even
at your father and brother's funeral,
he didn't show up.
He was very busy abroad at that time,
and really had no time.
It's not his fault.
How is it not his fault?
Shiya, you are just too kind.
Don't worry.
After you divorce,
I will definitely take good care of you.
Everything will get better.
I will send
your mother to the best sanatorium abroad.
Shiya.